[
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 32, 60, 83, 53?",
    "correctAnswer": "57",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "57",
      "58",
      "59",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 11, 82, 65, 86?",
    "correctAnswer": "61",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "61",
      "62",
      "63"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 26, 8, 74?",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "36",
      "37",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 60, 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "32",
      "33",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 37, 2, 77, 40?",
    "correctAnswer": "39",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "39",
      "40",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 87, 42, 93?",
    "correctAnswer": "74",
    "options": [
      "73",
      "74",
      "75",
      "76"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 15, 11?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "14",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 3, 35?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 27, 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 39, 83, 36, 78?",
    "correctAnswer": "59",
    "options": [
      "58",
      "59",
      "60",
      "61"
    ]
  }
]